this exercise has asked us to
add two strings together so we're going
to return
a first name and a last name as a single
string
let's initialize a local variable first
name
john and last name do
both of these local variables reference
strings and we want to
add these two strings together and
return a single string
we can use simple string concatenation
to do this
we can use the plus sign
to add the string reference by first
name and the string reference by last
name together
there's a problem with how we've written
our code on line 4 though
and we can see that if we run this
program
so let's output the string returned by
this concatenation
i'm going to hop over to the command
line and run the file
and you can see that although we've
added the two strings together into a
single string
the format is not what we want
we need to put a space between john and
go
now when we run our file we expect to
see the first name a space and then the
last name
and we do so that's string concatenation
another way that we could achieve this
result is with string interpolation
this allows us to insert these variables
into an existing string
using a special syntax we'll place
a hash and then a pair of curly braces
around our variable names
in order for string interpolation to
work we need the string to be wrapped
in double quotes rather than single
quotes
running our file again we see the same
output
so two simple ways that we can add
multiple strings together to return a
single string
are string concatenation and string
interpolation